I do feel like I'm reading a Dr Seuss
book right now I'm not gonna lie okay
all right I got I got a little bit far
with that with the uh you know Ryan did
you tell it to arrive or did it just do
that on its own I said like what did I
say do some catchy names or something
like that
[Music]
[Applause]
I just started during the countdown
yeah smooth yeah what do you think of my
new my new light it's a
oh dude I can see okay it's like pretty
good here I'll show you like the
difference it's like kind of noticeable
uh but only like if you see like the
before and after okay so this is like
with it on this is with it off
oh okay nice you can see it pretty soon
yeah it's pretty good and I could like
totally I don't know I feel like I want
to I think I have a little bit more I've
got a I've got a ring light right there
yeah you can kind of see when I block it
but I I think you know I don't think I'm
that much tanner than you so I think
it's got to be largely the yellow light
that's above me as well that makes the
difference yeah it could be I have like
the color temps all like because I was
having all sorts of weird like color
temp problems with it so I think I have
it like kind of kind of okay for now
got it worked out nice well sorry for
everybody who's actually listening on an
audio medium for this podcast if you
want to check out the color difference
of our skin and Joel's new uh light head
over to critical thinking podcast on
YouTube
um but with that
uh let's see what we got for today okay
so actually I really like this topic
today we're talking about
um hacker brain hacks and essentially
how to get over some of the things that
make bug Bounty so difficult
um so I think that's gonna be really
cool topic Joel I'm going to say check
out this document I did my research
today and and I have an outline with
beautiful bullet points with look at
these rhyming headers this is incredible
I mean most of the times most of the
time I'm the one who goes really crazy
on the like the Google Docs side so this
is uh this is nice this is cool man
thanks man I'm I'm I'm learning it here
too I'm flexing my uh Google Docs
muscles a little bit
um but
all right before we get into that
content let's check out some new stuff
uh I'll take the first one
um this is another we've mentioned this
guy on on the Pod before
demon Dev at D3 mon Dev I call I
mentioned I had to message him
afterwards and apologize because I
actually called him demand the last time
which is not what it is demon death
um but uh I follow this guy he puts out
really good stuff um one of the things
that I really liked that he put out
recently was um this website called
sequencediagram.org which allows you to
really cleanly and easily make these
sort of sequence diagrams where you've
got like
uh several you know pieces of of uh the
diagram vertically and then you've got
lines sort of jumping between each one
of them it's really helpful for
diagramming things like reverse proxies
and POC flows so I wanted to shout it
out on the podcast because
I think this could really help for
creating really in-depth pocs and making
sure your reports are really
understandable so we'll drop that link
down in the description definitely check
it out
um should really help yeah for sure and
this is something that I see a lot in
like the corporate type of space where
like engineering documents have this
this type of stuff all the time like
just to help you understand like what's
going on how stuff is supposed to work
so I think that this is like a great
step towards just like making your
reports more readable and making them
easier to triage you know yeah and at
the end of the day your reports are
going to be read by the Enterprise
security people so it's exactly what
they want to see yeah yeah super awesome
cool
um yeah so next thing uh we we've got uh
I'll jump I'll jump on over but uh Jay
Haddix previous podcast guess uh he
created this new tool called sub Recon
GPT and uh it's it's you know it's an
awesome implementation of like how do we
apply Ai and GPT and that kind of stuff
into like the bug Bounty hacking space
and so basically what he did is he
created a very very simple python script
that just takes a list of subdomains as
input
and then it feeds them into chat GPT and
it asks for similar subdomains and then
it'll use that to essentially like
generate like a like a word list uh or
something and then it will try and
resolve those domains so it's super
super awesome you know way of just like
kind of manipulating that data I think
it's really tricky to do this type of
stuff without some sort of like manual
intervention and like coming up with
like variation word lists and all that
kind of stuff is really really awesome
for finding like
um super Niche assets
um I I don't know if he wants to be
shouted out for this but a mutual friend
of ours who uh used to work with zyot
that's what I'll say I think you know
who I'm talking about well we'll bleep
it yeah so
is like a Recon God okay and the way
that he does this is by generating super
bespoke custom word lists for all of the
targets that he hacks on he'll like he
has this whole custom flow that he does
where he takes like data and he'll use
it to generate all these like custom
word lists and then he uses it to like
Brute Force either sub domains or
endpoints or whatever and he finds like
the craziest stuff by doing this yeah
it's really gnarly when you've got stuff
like that I remember I did I went that
far once I've done it a couple times but
it really paid off once at a live
hacking event for PayPal and I found
this application that was old and
everyone had forgotten about it and I
had to like go through you know all
these you know Hoops to get even get
access to it but once I did it was a
vulum all over the place right it was
just phones everywhere and I was like
man this thing is a cash cow I need to
like milk this for all it's worth right
and and so I got a hold of the
documentation for it and I was trying to
enumerate all these endpoints that they
were talking about in the documentation
that I confined right the functionality
and so I couldn't find it so what I
ended up doing was just parsing you know
um there's like some really old school
tool
um I can't remember the name of it but
essentially it goes out to the website
scrapes the uh you know the words used
and then uses that to you know uh do
some brute forcing and I did that and I
you know outlined the common structures
of the URLs and I brute forced and I got
so many hits and it probably resulted in
over 50k bounties from that one wow dude
and so yeah it's it's it's crazy what
what you can do when you really take
this extra level and go a little bit
deeper um I think this is a great tool
that does it also I'm a little salty
because this has been on my to-do list
for a really long time and if I wasn't
in the middle of a Renault right now
then I would absolutely be have had this
done
um yeah less than 100 lines it's super
awesome yeah um I think you probably
could even had chat GPD write this
itself to be to be honest yeah it's like
50 lines yeah
um this this is it kind of reminds me of
the asset note wordless but like one
step further because asset no word lists
are pulled from bigquery so they're
they're more like
you know modern so to speak right
they're more like up to date with like
what's going on right now like they're
based off of analytics and like query
data from like real requests over like
our the recent time span versus you know
just some word list is commonly used
stuff but not necessarily accurate to
the current like date
um and this is like you know that kind
of like bespokeness the like recency
that's like very like targeted one step
further so I think it's really awesome
and uh I'm probably gonna be throwing
this in my future sure I mean he
says he says for sure this is very beta
you know here so and if you look at the
code it's pretty much asking chat GPT
it's like
generate five subdomains similar to XYZ
I don't even think
yeah it's not it's not using Lane chain
or anything like that it's just using
the open AI uh a python API so there's
definitely rooms for improvement here if
anybody wanted to go and do like a pull
request on this I'm sure Jason would be
thrilled yeah yeah for sure
all right nice
um so next thing that I wanted to talk
about was
um we love to keep kaido in the Loof we
love to talk about kaido I think it's a
great tool it's the primary tool I'm
using right now for web proxying
um and uh love to see something like
this the Cyber Mentor actually put out a
video recently uh entitled this new web
hacking tool may replace burp suite and
I was like oh yeah here we go and he
does a um quite a long walk through of
of what it what it looks like you know
to use kaido use it up against a Target
so I was really thrilled to see that
it's like 11 minute video
um I think I think kaido is gaining more
and more traction and it's something
that you might want to go and subscribe
to right now and get the pro access
because it's only like I want to say
it's only like ten dollars yes it's
either ten dollars a month or 100 a year
depending on how you want to pay for it
and uh yeah I mean
a year
yeah it's ridiculous yeah so
if it's a cost thing for you
you know there's the there's the numbers
yeah for sure and um and you also have
an in ability right now to influence the
the
um
building of this product you can submit
issues you can talk to the team so
definitely don't miss out on that yeah
for sure it's not like there are large
features that like like I I use both a
lot now and it's like I'll definitely be
using kaido and I'll be like I wish
there was this feature from burp like
it'll be just like little like you know
quality of life things but like those
little things like they add up over time
and they're just like little features
that burp has just had more time to add
in
but there's also those same things in
kaido right yeah and so like for example
I every time I have to go back and burp
and I ha and I intercept a request and I
have to click forward forward forward
forward instead of just going directly
to the request and then heading forward
I'm like I hate this yes and and kaido
it just accused up all the requests you
can just click the request you want to
forward and just boom forward and it's
like amazing and uh and you know
switching projects is so much easier in
kaido I can do hacking from my
Chromebook on kaido you know while I'm
sitting in my living room so there's
there's a lot of really great stuff to
set up there
um and if you see those features that
aren't there just shoot a message to the
dev team and they're they're like super
responsive they hop on stuff right away
so really it's really awesome I actually
have a little thing set up with them now
where I just like drop them a loom video
so I don't even really have to do much
else I just like you get the private
line that's crazy outputs of URL I'm
just like boom and I don't even say
anything I just send them video and it
gets like put into an issue and it makes
it its way into the next Dev cycle so
that's what the Enterprise plan is
Jessica Enterprise I got the custom
support wow oh my gosh
um okay so actually so two more things
I'm sorry Joel I actually didn't put it
on the dock um
well the the one thing that I wanted to
talk about was I just wanted to give a
shout out to Yogurt um hacker one
co-founder he has been pumping out him
and the hacker one Dev team I will I
will include them all on that have been
pumping out some crazy features lately
and one I just want to say I have hacked
with yogurt before
nominal hacker very skilled and you know
the guys probably loaded at this point
you know having been a hacker one
co-founder and hacker one doing the way
that it is and he's still in there every
day running the engineering team with
with hacker one so mad respect there
um but two men have there been some nice
features getting pushed out lately
um they just released a command palette
for for hacker one which allows you to
really quickly navigate around and you
know submit new reports for the easy
open policy Pages really easily that's
amazing there's some encoding tools some
new analytics and and it's just it's
wonderful so if you haven't checked out
your hacker One dashboard recently or if
you're not seeing these tweets from
Gilbert
about
um you know the new features that are
going out definitely give him a follow
on Twitter
um and just to be just to be clear it's
j-o-b-r-t
uh yeah if you're looking it up
afterwards we'll we'll link it in there
we'll link it in the description cool um
yeah so this uh this this person uh
Justin Ells Elsie e-l-z-e
um he uh he tweeted out this awesome I I
don't know if he wrote this blog or or
what no I don't think so I'm not sure he
I think he's just linking to a cloud
cloud flare or actually this is actually
not even cloudflare this is something
yeah it's on iq.thc.org
um and just as the author is root so my
my assumption is this is just like
somebody's like oh self-hosted blog so
I'm not really sure he wrote this yeah
right however that's where the best
content is yeah it doesn't it doesn't
really matter however it does talk about
this really cool thing I never heard of
this I've heard of very similar things
um but it's called cloudflare D tunnels
or Cloud flared tunnels I'm not really
sure uh which one it is but uh
essentially if you're familiar with
ngrok uh ngr okay it's kind of like a
tunnel service that gives you a public
endpoint uh and you can tunnel it to
basically any like TCP port on your
Local Host
um and that's really awesome for a lot
of different things it's awesome from
like a developer perspective if you're
doing testing but it's also really
awesome from a hacker perspective where
you can host your pocs without having to
host your pocs
yeah you can absolutely do that and the
one of the reasons why I wanted to add
this to the list for today was
um this I think there's also some really
nice
um
functionality here and I'm realizing now
that you know cloudflare may have some
terms of services against this so you
know read the read the docs before you
do this but I was thinking this would be
amazing for
um you know hosting your your payloads
uh for hosting your your action and this
is less than a bug Bounty context but
more in just an actual like internal
assessment or you know red team
perspective where you're actually trying
to hack into an organization and we all
know that's probably the easiest way is
going to be to do social engineering or
some sort of like something like that
right so um this sort of thing is really
great because a lot of times your
domains get burned and stuff like that
or like you've got some uh next-gen
firewall that's blocking you know
domains that don't have a certain
accredation score whatever so um it's
really helpful to host your your C2 or
anything like that behind uh an
accredited domain like cloudflare so um
this is just a shout out for any of you
that are actually actively doing Red
Team stuff this might be be something
you can utilize in your in pivoting or
in your your day-to-day assessment yeah
yeah I also really like that this this
blog talks about that you can do like
SSH and stuff over this which is it's
just a really interesting
um use case I'm not sure if this adds
any sort of like implicit Security on
top of what you're doing I'm not sure
like what kind of access controls or
whatever you might be able to to perform
on this but um that's a really
interesting use case I'm not sure if you
could do that with angrock so seems like
it's just a raw T TCP thing yeah so so
pretty pretty interesting stuff
um definitely useful and I think I'm
gonna put this in my bookmarks for uh
for payloads and stuff
oh no they they do have they do have
secure yeah yeah they they have TLS cool
nice okay so that's it for the news
section
onto the meat onto the meat and potatoes
so
um
yeah I guess all all preface this by
saying I'm a full-time bug Bounty Hunter
and
um
I guess being a full-time bug Bounty
Hunter you have a lot more
I guess mental challenges with bug
Bounty or you have different mental
challenges let me let me just put that
there
um because one it's your it's your
livelihood and you're doing it every day
and it becomes your job
um but uh you know on the other hand
you're also not having to juggle bug
bounty in your in your full-time job and
that sort of thing so at some point I
wanna I wanna do and I've I've got a
little section at the end of this doc
I'm not sure if we'll get it to it today
about just some of the tips that I've
learned from doing bug Bounty full-time
and I know we talked about it a little
bit on the full-time bug Bounty episode
but I've got some other other stuff as
well that we'll get to but the main the
main focus for today was like mentality
stuff
um so I broke it down
into three sections you can see them in
the doc Joel before hacking during
hacking and after hacking okay and these
are the kind of I just kind of
brainstormed for a little while and then
I used you know chat GPT to come up with
some snazzy names for each section
um about what kind of struggles you
might be running into at each one of
these phases
um on your hacking I do feel like I'm
reading a Dr Seuss book right now I'm
not gonna lie okay all right I went a
little bit far with uh with the uh you
know Ryan did you tell it to Rhyme or
did it just do that on its own I said
like what did I say do some catchy names
or something like that for XYZ so I
don't know we'll we'll see what we got
okay first one
um this is in the before hacking section
um I see this one all the time and I've
uh you know me AKA chat gbt AKA Dr Seuss
uh has named this one procrastination
education okay so essentially the topic
behind this is like
you are scared to start hacking because
you think you're gonna fail
so you just educate educate educate
educate educate as a form of
procrastination
against you know doing actual hacking
see this all the time some people
affectionately call it tutorial hell
um or not affectionately call it
tutorial hell
um but this is definitely a pitfall and
definitely something that that yeah a
lot of people run into what do you think
about that yeah um I think we've touched
on this a couple different times
um it's really really challenging
because when you're new to this you're
like what what do I even start what do I
look at like what do I need to know
right and that's those are like
completely valid questions and ones that
you need to answer but the question is
like how much do you need to answer it
right like do you need to fully
understand every aspect of the owasp top
10 or every like every conceptual part
of like
a csrf or do you just need to know like
what it looks like and how to exploit it
right and I think there's a fine line
between like how far you need to Deep
dive on learning a topic versus
how far you need to dive just to exploit
it and
um I think this happens a lot especially
with new people where they just want to
like absorb knowledge and keep learning
and keep learning and that's great but
like when you're gonna start hacking
like you gotta you gotta Branch at some
point and and start you can keep
learning but like you got to start
hacking and putting that knowledge to
use because that's what's really going
to solidify it in your brain
yeah I totally agree and and I think one
of the things I've told people is like
hey um you know do your basic
introductions into
how websites work you know I have this
flow that I go go through with with the
people that I'm teaching which
disclaimer is not anyone that's ever
messaged me online I cannot take remote
mentorships please stop messaging me
about that
um I really appreciate you reaching out
but like I only Mentor people that I
know in real life and so sorry about
that I'm the same way by the way like
it's nothing personal it's just like
it's a it's a large time commitment and
like we want to set expectations
accordingly we don't want to like set
set you up for failure set you up to
expect something that's not gonna happen
so we just kind of have signed it off
entirely and we basically only do
mentorships on like very rare one-off
cases and it's usually people that we
know
yeah so so feel free to shoot me a
message if you have a question appointed
question or something like that I'll
definitely get to it but I can't just do
a formal mentorship with everyone okay
so what I was going to say though was
when I am mentoring people I always walk
them through this flow of like okay
um you know first we gotta understand
how a website works and how you know
HTTP works and how DNS works and we walk
through all that whole flow of what
happens when you put a you know a URL in
your browser and then they understand
that and they understand how to view it
in burp they understand how to you know
modify uh parameters you know they
understand how to use an HTTP proxy
um and then you know I have them start
working on uh portsmaker wsa
um and and once they kind of get through
that I say a little bit into that you
know once they've gone through the
access control section or the broken uh
or the business logic section
I I say okay now we need to start
pivoting part of your time from from a
very very early stage into actual
hacking so take 10 of your time do
hacking take 20 of your time do hacking
all the way up to 50 60 70 of your time
doing hacking and it's gonna feel like
crap in the beginning because you're not
going to know what you're doing and
you're going to be looking at requests
that don't make any sense and but just
being in the HTTP request reading the
headers reading the body being curious
understanding how functionality in the
UI maps to API requests in the back end
that is the meat you need to be so
comfortable with that before you can
effectively do hacking and the more time
you spend that's that's all you know
that's all more experience that you've
got and and that will serve you every
single one even if you don't find
anything if you don't understand
anything that will serve you in becoming
a better hacker periodically as as you
continue gradually as you continue to
grow so don't neglect that time or else
you'll never get anywhere yeah no and
you'll be stuck in tutorial Health yeah
100 like that's just like asking like
why does this work or how does this work
or like where does this value come from
is super instrumental to like
understanding the core deep
functionality of how an application is
is functioning and where data is going
and all that kind of stuff
um cool yeah so so you got to start
hacking right but here this is like the
next thing that I see like second most
common thing for new hackers analysis
paralysis it's like what program do I
pick what do I hack on what do I focus
on like ah man this is this is like such
a common thing we talked a little bit
about this during the how to pick a good
program
um but I think especially when you're
new and you're trying to pick pick like
the first program to hack on just pick
like whatever sounds interesting right
um I I think it's almost more important
not to really focus on bounties bounties
are very alluring it's very like
tempting to like want that like big high
Cash Money prizes and stuff and I'm not
saying that it's impossible to get those
on larger programs that typically have
the higher Bounty tables but it's gonna
be more challenging because there's a
lot more people who have come before you
who have looked at that stuff a lot more
than you have and they have that leg up
and you can get there for sure but it's
going to take more time and you may not
get the sort of instant gratification or
satisfaction that you're looking for on
one of those larger programs so I
recommend just picking whatever sounds
interesting because that's going to help
you with the natural drive for hacking
pick a website that you're familiar with
or like a tool that you've heard of or
something that would be like like for
some people it's oh I want to hack the
government okay so Focus it's on a DOD
program don't worry about bounties they
have a huge program huge scope just like
hack some DOD stuff then you can be like
yeah I hack the government you know cool
whatever you want like for bragging
rights you know or like you know
whatever service you wanna you wanna
hack like that that's what I would
recommend
I I I sort of agree with that Joel I I
think video D is a little bit of an
exception I do mention the dod as well
to most people just because it does give
you some sort of payment you know you're
you get to say Hey you know I hacked the
dod and that feels cool and that's nice
I normally recommend people to start
from the beginning with Bounty programs
because and skip the the VDP stage
because it feels so much better to get
an actual Bounty yeah right and and some
people some people will say hey I just
want a valid bug and you know what
that's fine maybe vdps are for you then
but my suggestion is to actually go and
get an actual Bounty
um and if it takes extra time great but
here's the problem with the with with
the VDP programs one nobody looks at
them and so uh you know you can go on
there and you may be able to find some
booms but you're not going to get a good
um indicator of how deep you need to go
to find bugs on an actual bug Bounty
program
um yeah and two obviously you're not
getting paid for your time which is it's
not going to help you with some of the
other stuff we'll talk about a little
bit later which is bug Bounty being a
results
um results for money based system right
it's a it's some would call it a
meritocracy but I'll say it it's a it's
it's a results for money based system so
if you spend a bunch of time you don't
get the results you don't get any money
right
um and so I think that's something that
kind of takes some time to get used to
and something that you can
um you know sort of edge into from the
beginning yeah
um I will say from before Joel uh that
was episode 13 how to pick a good bug
Bounty program we probably shouldn't
spend too much more time uh too much
time on how to actually you know pick a
program on here I will say one tip from
that episode go go watch the whole
episode and understand it but one tip
that I'll pull away from that is if you
can hack a website that you use yeah
yeah and and I'll clarify I I don't know
if I I may have misspoken I'm not really
advocating that you pick vdps over bug
Banning programs I think I would always
try and pick a book value program except
in you know like we talked about like
maybe the education OD but what I want
to say is don't focus on how high the
bounties are right so if it's like 1K
crits versus three crits versus 5K crits
yeah we all want a 5k crit but a
bounty's a bounty and it's really just
like what interests you if the thing in
the beginning if the thing you want to
hack has a 1K Bounty that's fine like I
would I would push towards that and then
like once once you feel more confident
then like go hack whatever and and don't
care so much about what the target is
but for that initial drive it's really
it's really important to like you know
want to hack what you're hacking
yeah totally agree man okay next one is
um automation Obsession and now I'm
feeling silly about all these automation
automation obsession is the next one
very aptly named because
um this is actually a pitfall that I
fell into
um and I got very fortunate
um and I that I actually got a crazy
automation bug uh which got me started
my first bug was a 4K subdomain takeover
which is high even by today's standards
um
but uh what I wanted to say on this one
was a lot of people will feel like they
need to build out their whole Recon
automation system and do all this
programming and a lot of these people
are programmers by the way so it makes
sense that you want to do the thing that
you you know already know how to do
I would say do not do that if you if you
really want to get good at this because
um you know automation is a great is a
great field and is something that you
can absolutely make a lot of bounties
off of
um but first you need to know how to
hack and for this I will go ahead and
refer you all and we're going to talk
about this a little bit more in the
Recon section but the point of this
automation is to find volts right and
you're not going to know how to find
volumes until you actually find
vulnerabilities so so I would recommend
putting the automation aside even if
it's small automation like I want to be
able to take this thing from GAO and put
it into something else which is a part
of normal hacking
um I would say hold off on that as much
as you can when you're hacking hack and
when you're automating automate but try
not to mix the two too much yeah cool
yeah so for the next one I wish this
would Rhymes and was more fun to talk
about but to imposter syndrome it's uh
that's just that's just uh you know
that's not an easy one to swallow
um I'm just gonna say that it doesn't it
doesn't go away it gets easier to deal
with uh because you can understand it
and spot it much easier
um as you deal with it more but it's
kind of one of those things that's
always going to be there and you just
have to figure out the right ways to
like
stop thinking about it or stop like you
know just like
thinking and thinking and thinking and
and and you know mulling it over in your
brain and just like oh I'm not good
enough oh like I love this fomo and
whatever it's like just you know go back
to to like the early beginner tips right
like procrastination education analysis
paralysis okay stop thinking about it
stop trying to learn so much just do it
right yeah and the Imposter syndrome
thing I think as well is like it's
something that
it's something that you fight with while
you're hacking but it's also something
that you fight with before you're
hacking and that's why I have it in the
before your hacking section here
before you're hacking if it's preventing
you from hacking I'm not good enough to
do that
you need to punch that in the face you
need to get upset about at that imposter
syndrome and say listen
that's wrong uh hacking is not a a
you're good enough or you're not good
enough sort of thing it's a it's a
process and and I I'm saying this from
being you know having done this a lot
guys this is not some wishy-washy you
know you can do it go get it Tony
Robbins BS right it this is this is
actually
a fact you know spending time uh in the
application learning the application is
a pivotal part of this so even if you
don't feel like you're good enough yet
get in there start learning get your
hands on it yeah and it's not like that
meritocracy like where people think like
all the more time I spend like I'm for
sure gonna find something like there are
going to be times where you're gonna
spend a ton of a ton of time and effort
looking for something and you're not
gonna find something and you're going to
feel extremely like beat up and worn
down and you just have to remember like
that's normal okay you didn't do
anything wrong like that is literally
just part of the process and you have to
realize that you're you're hunting for
gold in a in a river you know you're
you're like it's like the 1850s it's the
Gold Rush yeah needle in a haystack and
there's no guarantee that needle's there
you know like there's five Haystacks
which one is the needle and start
looking a very valuable meal it's a
Golden Needle like yeah
Golden Needle
needle and then he's yeah somewhere
there's an analogy in there somewhere
something like that but yes like just
remember like none of this is guaranteed
like we hope to find bad vulnerabilities
so that we get paid out but none of it
is ever like for sure and so if you
don't find anything
that's kind of a good thing right like
that's that's kind of that's kind of a
good thing
yeah and I want to say this as well
um there are a lot of of people that for
most of you let me just say there are a
lot of people that are a lot less
skilled than you that are getting
bounties right now I can I can promise
you that so
get out there and do it okay next one
for the before hacking section was
motivation deprivation yeah
um and
um this is this is a sort of a a
this is sort of in a situation that kind
of comes into play when after you found
a dupe after you haven't been finding
anything for a while and you're starting
up hacking again it can be really
challenging to like
take on the huge task of looking at a
big application and that sort of thing
and what I would encourage you all on
this one is to just stay stay curious
okay stay be in it don't be focused too
much on the bounties don't be focused
too much on on the finding something be
focused on becoming an expert on this
specific application
um one of the live hacking events that I
that I participated in a while back I
spent so much time on this one
application two weeks every day in the
JS files finding everything I possibly
could and when I got to that live
hacking I was like you know what I bet I
know everything about this application I
bet no one here knows more about this
application than I do so I was I put a
message out in the chat I was like hey
anybody want to teach me something that
I don't know about this application
right and I got taken to school that day
like like it but it's that that sort of
confidence is the confidence that you
need like by the time that that life
hacking event day came around I felt
like I knew everything about that
application but the cool the part about
it is you never will know everything
about the application and so you can
keep on so I had probably pushed through
two or three layers at that point of
yeah I think I found everything on this
right and I I said well let me do
another double check let me do another
double check let me do another double
check and then I got to this point and I
was and then I still got taken to school
by some of the other people that are at
the live hacking event so
there's always going to be more defined
um
so yeah diving that's super amazing and
I think you don't have to like don't
don't take away from that that you have
to be at a live hacking that to have
that kind of moment just like yeah ask
yourself like when you feel like you're
at the edge of knowledge be like is
there anything else that I don't know
about or I haven't fully explored and
that's where your note taking and all
that kind of stuff will really come into
play
dude I actually want to share this
really cool tidbit I mentioned a guy a
while back I shot it shouted them out
um that I said hey you know write down
all your attack vectors and go and he
messaged me the other day and because he
said I think I found everything
um and I was like okay do it again and
he's like okay I trust you man he found
four more bugs one of them which was
exactly and I was like dude you rock way
to continue persevering and not only
that he had it written down it was there
so cool
um okay one more thing I wanted to talk
about on this this is a little bit of
live hacking event hack
um that Mariah and I uh put together for
those of you that don't know Mariah is
my wife
um and so when I we were going into live
hacking events
um I guess sometimes it's it's easy to
get overwhelmed it's easy to not feel
motivated especially when you're on the
live hacking event circuit and you're
doing them every month or every other
month it can get kind of intense
and so um one of the things Mariah came
up with was this goal system for me so
we would say okay Justin
um you know here are the tears okay at
this tier uh you know you can
do XYZ so like for example one of one of
my tiers uh for the Vegas Allied hanging
last year was to get a hot tub so if I
earn more than x amount boom hot tub if
I earn more than y amount boom Cruise
you know
um and so like setting tiers and goals
for yourself can be really motivating
and if you you can see that sort of
prize in the distance it's easier to
stay on top of it and remember what
you're hacking for so that's a nice
little hack
um you know Define couple week Sprints
if you're not doing a live hacking event
say all right I'm gonna hack for the
next three weeks if at the end of this
three weeks I've submitted bugs that uh
you know sum up to X thousand dollars
then I'm gonna go out to a nice dinner
or something like that I think that can
be really nice yeah for sure I was gonna
go into goals and stuff but I think it's
we're going to talk about it a little
bit more in the during hacking session
so so let's dive into that yeah um so
yeah during hacking um so like the first
one automation Obsession now this is
like a recurring thing yeah so and I'll
go yeah go ahead I copy I copied that
one in there I copied that one in there
from the other one just to just uh throw
a curveball at you Joel um I copied that
one in from the before session as well
and here's why this should this one
should be pretty quick
I often found when I was trying to shift
away from automation Obsession that I
was uh I would get into hacking I'd be
like all right yeah cool I'm doing this
hacking thing right and then and then I
like find something interesting and I'm
like oh man I need to like
I need to scan for this you know or I
need to like
be able to
um evaluate for this vulnerability very
very quickly and so then I would stop
what I was doing instead of saying in my
zone in my mode hacking I would you know
fire up Python and start trying to
automate that and that's an obsession
with automation
um don't do that when you're hacking
hack when you're automating automate
take notes you know on what things you
want to automate come back to it later
but stay in the zone because when when
you're in the zone when you have the
application context in your brain you
need to minimize distractions and so
automation can be one of those
distractions yeah for sure notes notes
notes notes write everything down come
back to it later yeah yeah cool um Recon
cognizance reconnaissance cognizance
that's a there's a mouthful there you go
yeah
um so basically just like there's
nothing that really Rhymes well with
recall like Recon since Recon
yeah yeah but it's not like that yeah so
so Recon reconnaissance yeah so like how
do you how do you like get your brain
around Recon in like a meaningful way
right I think
um it's a really easy trap to fall into
this like Recon hole because for one
there are so many tools that are just re
like literally just for Recon subdomain
brute forcing uh path Traverse path
brute forcing host brute forcing uh
fuzzers you know everything like
scanners yeah it's all like you know
it's a bunch of brute forces and that's
cool and stuff but like
I think it's really easy to fall down a
rabbit hole where you you're like I
don't get it I ran all seven tools that
I have and I haven't found a bug yet
what's going on I guess I'm just gonna
go to the next Target right and like
there are a lot of hackers who do that
which should tell you that if you don't
do that you're gonna find the stuff that
they missed so I think Recon is really
good for identifying attack surface and
like seeing what things might be
interesting to poke at or or maybe
taking some notes and and checking those
things out later
but once you have like you know 10
things or whatever not even like you
know once you have a couple things just
start looking into them and you're gonna
find other stuff as you look because the
Recon isn't really like the end-all
be-all some bugs do end there but but
the majority I say don't
yeah and and I just love this quote and
we clipped it and we put it at the
beginning of episode 12 with J Haddix
probably one of the most valuable
takeaways that he he he we have from
that episode from the Recon God himself
Jay Haddix he says I make all these
talks about Recon to help you find more
apps to hack right that's the goal so do
your recon until you've found an
interesting app to hack and then just
hack that App instead of doing recon
internally
um that's that's my take there are some
people that have different takes and
there are people that subscribe to a lot
more Recon heavy methodology but at the
end of the day even people like nogly
right
um you know he's a big Recon guy but
when it comes to the life hacking events
the way he kills it the way he ranks top
is he gets his head on straight and he
focuses and he hacks the main app dive
deep very important cool let's talk
about uh goals a little bit shall we
okay okay so let me let me let me just
say this one it says bad rabbit holes
rip your goals
come up with that no this one was me I'm
not gonna I can't even play this one on
chat gbt
um this one's for me uh bad rabbit holes
rape your goals so let me just explain
this one
um a while ago on the Pod I I think we
were talking about a treat from rezzo
um and I had said I actually think it's
good to rabbit hole and I do still hold
that but I do want to mention uh that I
think there's a little bit more Nuance
to the topic and I would love to have
res on sometimes to debate it but
um essentially my current place is that
you have to be able to identify what
these bad rabbit holes are
um and
um I've got a couple little notes here
and I'd be interested in hearing your
your thoughts as well Joel but
essentially some ways to identify bad
rabbit holes are the following one it
does not expand your scope so if this
rabbit hole that you're going down
doesn't give you access to
more scope you know maybe you're trying
to figure out a way to access a specific
application by like getting an account
there registering an account or
something like that that might be a good
rabbit hole
um uh but you know if you're doing
something that doesn't really expand
your scope and doesn't meet any of the
following conditions then it might not
be a good rabbit hole the next one is
low impact it doesn't
it doesn't mesh with the application's
threat model you need to understand what
kind of things the application finds
valuable and what will happen at the end
of The Rabbit Hole it needs to be a
destination Rabbit Hole it needs to be
one of those holes that goes down and
then you pop off on the other side you
know it can't be one that just goes
straight down and then you die at the
bottom of the hole okay so you need to
have a goal with where your rabbit hole
should lead you
um and uh if you can't clearly see that
it's a very big risk to
go down that rabbit hole Yeah the next
one was
um non-deterministic if you think that
there is a
if you don't know I guess this is kind
of similar to the low impact one but if
you don't have a good idea of whether
this is going to work out or not or you
don't see a clear path to whether it's
going to work out or not then this may
be a tricky rabbit hole right
um if you if you have a very clear
condition like oh I just need to bypass
this one piece and then I've got like an
ssrf or this one piece and then I've got
you know an ATO then that that could be
a good example but if it if it's like uh
you know I think once I bypass this one
piece then there could be like maybe
there's other controls in place but very
likely you know you know if you if you
you know hear yourself having that
little internal conversation then could
be a bad Rabbit Hole
um you have any other thoughts on bad
rabbit holes ripping your goals yeah
yeah so I think
um I agree with both of you like rabbit
holes are both useful and not useful
um and like you said there are there are
key things that can really help you
identify whether or not you're going
down a Bad Rabbit Hole so to speak
um I think
it's really
easy to like be able to see it from both
sides so if you're like it is for
example
um something that catches me a lot is
account creation uh proxying or
something if I'm proxy a mobile app I
might be able to proxy the whole app
except for like just the beginning
request or something or like the the
account creation was and while that is a
really useful attack scenario it's also
only one piece of like the whole
application it's only one piece of the
flow
so instead of like rabbit holding down
and like spending three hours trying to
figure out why I can't proxy this one
request just write it down
move on right come back to it later
and that that's a great that's a great
point because that does expand your
scope a little bit right that expands
your scope to account creation but it
doesn't vastly expand your scope right
and so it's it's very limited right
limited scope expansion right could be a
bad word right and not only that you
might be restricted by like oh it's a
one-time thing like depending on what
the volt is you have to think about like
what might be the worst case scenario
like if I can imagine of just like being
able to get access to this scope and if
it's not like the worst possible thing
or worse than other things you could
think of again just write it down and
come back to it later because you're
spending a lot of that valuable time
just like trying to debug something when
you could be spending that like doing
hacking and expanding your scope and
like learning about the application all
that kind of stuff totally agree on this
just want to provide a disclaimer
I'm pretty sure this is what Reza would
say from the beginning anyway so yeah
okay maybe I don't agree with you I
don't know yeah I did agree with what
you said you know
yeah you know I'm pretty sure this is
what Reza was talking about from the
beginning anyway but you know just
throwing that out there I I think I
think there are good rabbit holes in and
think there are bad rabbit holes
um and these are some descriptors of a
bad rap yeah yeah hopefully that'll be
okay and I will say I have I have this
one little note before I move on
you gotta trust your intuition on some
of these things too and this is not as
much for you newer hackers
um but for you more experienced hackers
let's say maybe you've looked at
30 to 50 plus applications
um trust your intuition though because
sometimes
your brain knows something that you
don't know and if you think man I just
really can't get this one piece of the
application out of my mind
take the hour and just dive in and get a
little deeper because I actually have
found some cool stuff by doing that and
this goes back to the Curiosity thing as
well sometimes you just want to do cool
[__] and you know even if that doesn't
end up with a vault if you understand
how the specific process works and that
makes that feels good that feels cool to
you definitely go after it before we
move on to the to the next
um the next thing I did want to talk
about goals really quick because this is
talked about like talking about like
ripped to your goals and stuff but but
goals are like really really important
in my opinion about like for for hacking
right I I think this is I think one of
the most important things you can do
when you're hacking at Target is set set
a specific goal okay I want to become a
super admin I want to take over this
account I want to uh get an xss uh
whatever it is right like I just
wrote set your goal polls
okay well that's what we're calling you
can Workshop okay no it's great set your
goal polls yeah yeah so yeah just set
goals I think goals are really important
um even if it may seem unattainable in
the beginning
having some sort of frame of reference
just like how with earnings you have
goals just so you have something to look
towards something to like picture and
think about goals when hacking are
really important as well because it's
going to help you frame your entire
reference about the application what
could I do with this endpoint what can I
do with that endpoint oh this is weird
functionality what can I do with that if
you frame all of that towards your
singular goal it's going to make you
think much more creative and it's going
to help you get to that goal much much
easier
yeah they totally agree with that one of
the the biggest bounties I've ever seen
paid out in person was from a uh I don't
even know what they were called at that
point Verizon media Yahoo oath payout
where they set a goal and they said hey
anyone who can do arbitrary account
takeover gets
you know 50k bonus or something
ridiculous like that right and somebody
you know lo and behold someone did it
because they set up a goal so this is
actually a tip for the the program side
as well if there are any program
managers listening to this pod and I
know there are
um definitely you know consider setting
specific bonuses for things that are
high value to you like arbitrary account
takeover or or like full breed internal
SSR app or something like that because
that is a great way to motivate hackers
in a very specific direction grammarly
is a great example of that grammarly has
a 100K I think it's 100K if you can read
a secret within a specific account or
document or something and that's just in
their policy page you know it's just
been there so if you want to you know
get that 100K like frame everything you
can to get that I've heard it's very
difficult so we gotta go after that we
gotta check that out I think that'll be
cool okay um the last one in the during
hacking section is called impact lacked
impact
um and this is this is sort of situation
that you can follow into where you swing
to the other side and you get too
curious or you get too Focus focused on
just some weird functionality that is
like funky and odd but doesn't
necessarily have impact I see this all
the time with new Hunger Hunters like oh
I found this like directory listing and
there's all these directories in here
and like you know oh I can access all
these files and this is amazing this is
a film no that's that's not a vault um
because there's no impact to the
customer so before you DM someone and
you say hey Justin
um is this a volume you should ask
yourself
why do I think this is a vault and you
need to be able to answer that question
what can I do
that the company doesn't want me to be
able to do and there could be an
argument made that you know the company
doesn't want you to be able to see all
their directories in the directory
listing right to that I would say
that that doesn't meet the the impact
standards but
you need to outline that sort of thought
that sort of mentality
um from the very beginning and make sure
that the thing you're going after
actually has impact to the to the
company yeah yeah and on that you got to
understand the threat model right so
like if you are trying to explain this
to a company the best way to prove
impact is to explain it in a way that
demonstrates impact okay and so like
think about what does the company care
about is it user data is it their data
is it intellectual property
whatever right like hey well but most of
the time that's not gonna be a directory
listing unless that directory listing
has something in it that is impactful
right and so I think like instead of
just reporting a directory listing look
at the stuff in the directory listing
and see if you can find something more
impactful maybe then consider just
reporting that as is but I I don't think
like that would meet my criteria either
in terms of like you know uh oh I'm
gonna report this and like get a sick
Bounty like you're gonna get like 100
Bounty you know
for sure totally agree and not nothing
against 100 bounties you know 100
bounties 100 yes and I and I would I
would say you know if it meets the
organization's threat model and they've
outlined that in the policy then you
should absolutely report that take the
100 bucks help the company a win-win-win
but um
also that's not going to be the case a
large percentage of the time for
something like directory listings cool
okay so after hacking yeah after hacking
burnout
no you got to say the whole title you
can't skip that
after hacking the burnout turnout
there you go after hacking the burnout
turnout
um okay so you you want to take this one
sure yeah so I I think you have you're
gonna have lots to say on this
um I definitely have dealt with burnout
so much
um it it definitely comes from different
areas sometimes it's that you've been
doing a ton of hacking and you're not
getting a ton of bounties
um sometimes it's that you have been
doing a ton of hacking and you haven't
gotten a single Bounty um sometimes it's
that you know you've been uh looking at
a Target you submitted a bunch of cool
things turns out they were all internal
dupes
um there's a lot of different reasons
that you can get burnout
um and I think again kind of like
imposter syndrome you you have to
remember this is completely normal and
it's not like you've done anything wrong
to feel this way um burnout is like a
very normal thing
it's it's probably more important to try
and figure out what caused it and how
you can try and avoid it or ease that
burn out in the future
yeah I totally agree there has to be a
mending process and a maintenance
process
um and so you know The Mending piece is
like ah all right I'm burnt out how do I
get out of this funk right and the
maintenance process is how do I not get
burnt out in in the first place and a
lot of this a lot of the the things that
for me with bug Bounty that causes
burnout is this whole results for money
impact right like if I if I put all this
effort in at my day job and something
doesn't work out I still get a salary
you know if I'm a salaried employee but
if I put all this results in and or all
this effort in and get no results out in
Buck Bounty NADA you know and and that's
that's a that's what happens from a
material basis however you got to
understand that for every moment you're
putting into not finding a a bug and
getting a bounty that's another minute
that you will not have to spend until
you find your next your next you know
book right so it's not actually
uh useless it's not actually wasted time
it's just a part of the process right
and you're learning a lot when it's
happening
absolutely and you're learning a ton and
that's that's very very tangible and
this is one of the things that I I've
kind of talked to some of my friends
that are that are starting trying to
like upstart some some local businesses
and trying to do sales right
um for every like X customers that you
talk to and you get declined like have
something that makes it feel worthwhile
like pay yourself an extra dollar or
something like that if you have startup
money or like you know say all right if
I get 30 customers that say no to me
today I'm gonna just go get some
Chick-fil-A or something like that right
you know have some sort of metric that
makes it still feel like even though
that person said no your time wasn't
wasted and the same thing happens here
with with bug Bounty you know for every
100 attack vectors that you try or for
every 50 attack factors that you try
whatever it is you know do something
that that's care self-care so that you
don't end up getting burnt out I was
just thinking about like uh you're at
your 29th rejection of the day you're
you got three calls left and you're like
please just say no I want the
Chick-fil-A
yeah the worst scenario is like you have
a goal for 10 calls you know and then
you get the hot tub or 10 yeses then you
get the hot tub and then you get your
call for 30 you know 30 rejections and
you got 29.9 and you should walk away
because you're done for the day it's
like [__] you know cool man no that's
fine so do you have like
um like what do you use for like
personal tactics to like deal with this
because I'm sure you you deal with
burnout all the time yeah yeah I do and
it's hard um I think post life hacking
event I spent uh at least a week of
downtime and a lot of times I mean we'll
talk about this a little bit later I've
got some stuff to catch up on you know
after the live hacking event season
um just some responsibilities that have
uh Fallen to the side but
um as far as you know my long-term
solutions for for Burnout I've actually
suffered from burnout very little
um in my my three three years yeah as a
full-time book Bounty Hunter and I I
attribute that largely to having a
stable you know marriage and personal
life and then also to prayer and to
finding my identity in something that is
not bug Bounty because I I have the the
inclination to say like man if I'm not
crushing in bug bounty
I suck I am worthless you know and and
you know it's not something I'm actively
saying but it's something that I'm
feeling right and so you really have to
address that first you've got to put
your your
hope your your identity your self-worth
in something that is not your work
because especially in Buck Bounty it's
extremely dangerous there is a whole
team of people on the other side of the
computer whose job it is non-stop you're
nine to five every single day to make
your job impossible right that is that's
a lot of that is a lot of pushback right
and um and so you know keeping that in
mind and you know finding your identity
elsewhere really good also for me I find
it really helpful to get out in the sun
play some volleyball you know have a
decent workout routine spend time with
with loved ones and family even though
you know you're in the middle of a live
hacking event or a really intense
hacking season
um and that will just allow you to move
refreshed into the the next time you're
well earned hot tub
exactly yeah yeah yeah you get that
first set of goal get a hot tub then
make that happen
get in the hot tub that's the solution
everything else doesn't matter once
you're in the hot tub exactly at all
costs get the hot tub awesome no
um yeah do you have any comments on that
or do you want to hop today um no I mean
I I think I have a lot of the same type
of just like try and separate yourself
away from it
um this is again we talked about this in
in both the before hacking and the
during hacking but bug Bounty is not a
guaranteed thing right finding a bug
finding a security vulnerability
especially a critical one not guaranteed
and you have to remember that like we
are trying to like almost do the
impossible here right we are we are
pushing against talented security teams
here to try and find the holes that they
missed and when you find something
that's awesome but it's not guaranteed
and you can't like beat yourself up for
not for like not finding a myth like a
mythical thing that may or may not exist
you know it's like nothing that you did
could have controlled that like and made
it appear right it either exists or it
does in and what really matters is
whether or not you can identify it and
that's like completely separate from
like
finding it you know what I mean like I I
think like you can always like just take
your notes and stuff you can always keep
hunting but
um don't don't beat yourself up for like
a good security team being good you know
like that's uh that that's kind of an
unjustified reason to beat yourself up
yeah totally agree
um Okay so we've got two left in after
hacking
um I know you got to bounce here in a
bit Joel so we'll try to move through
them pretty quickly because I want you
to be around for this report that I want
to tell you about
um
responsibility volatility is the next
one
um and essentially this is what I was
talking about before where you get so
pulled into hacking that you've
neglected other responsibilities whether
that be your relationship with your
significant other whether it be your
chores you know the dishes the lawn
whatever
um it's very easy to get
focused and in the zone and then let
everything else fall behind and it's not
sustainable and when you do that and you
let all the things fall behind and you
let that get and you don't you know
communicate well with your spouse or you
don't hire someone to do your lawn or
something like that then it becomes
um that's a very easy way to get burnt
out because you'll come out of the
hacking thing you'll be like ah and
you'll have like a panic reaction and
then you'll be stressed out trying to
get all this stuff done and get back up
caught up and it's just an easy really
easy way to get yourself in a rough
situation so don't become so fixated
that you know you're not spending time
with your loved ones that you're not
carrying with your responsibility yeah
for sure it's it's important to treat
bug Bounty like a job if it is your
full-time job right like don't don't let
those hours like abuse you just you know
take it in a reasonable Pace don't like
be working 15 hours a day every single
day unless you feel like that's gonna
really drive the results and I still
wouldn't recommend doing that at a lot
for like a long period of time know what
I mean like that's uh that's a lot yeah
well one of the best things about being
full-time bug Bounty is you have a lot
of freedom you know and so make sure
you're not squandering that because
we're all especially if you're younger
you know you're a Time billionaire if
you're not a money billionaire right and
so you know you're training your time
for money and you know you you can trade
your money for time when you do stuff
like you know pay people to do your lawn
or whatever
um make sure you're not squandering that
asset of like I can make good money and
still have a lot of freedom
um and I think that's something that
I've learned recently and something that
I'm struggling to implement right now
because I'm in the middle of a Renault
too so my time is getting really
crunched but once I get at it done with
this um you know rental property Renault
uh I think I'll be a lot more enjoying
the freedom that comes along with being
full-time but yeah for sure all right
and for the last one payout phase out
I think this one is a lot more relevant
for like the full-time Hunters but uh
really this is you know you you you're
waiting for a bounty things start to
slow down you're like I got the report
in let's just wait and see when they pay
it and and see how I feel but like that
it's a really easy trap to fall into
oh yeah yeah and I think I think um I
think
it's very tempting and and there's
there's two sides of this because one
hand you kind of want to validate your
threat model before you spend a bunch of
time on an organization that doesn't
that you think you understand their
threat model and you don't really
understand so that's one you know that's
the positive side on waiting for the
Banning but the negative side is like
you get into an app you find some great
bugs you write them up you send them in
and then you just lose all context on
that app and that's not that's not great
because a lot of the time if there's a
volumes in a specific area there's
probably more volumes there so go back
don't get too over excited about the
volume that you found that you you miss
other bones
um and and hit it again because uh
there's likely other bones there yeah
yeah super super awesome advice and um
notes you know take notes if you're if
you've just like submitted a bug and
you're like this is gonna be a sick
payout and you're not sure what to do
next
check your notes go look at the other
stuff that you wrote down and you didn't
feel like you had fully investigated
that's a great opportunity to go look at
some of that other stuff now that you've
kind of completed you know your your
train of thought and finished reporting
the bug you know
yeah
um Joel I know you got to bounce here in
a second feel free to to leave if you
want I can wrap things up but I did want
to I did want to talk about this one
report um I put it in the dock it's a
one that got disclosed this week on
LinkedIn
um and the title of it entire database
of emails exposed through urn injection
so when I saw this I was like what the
heck is URL that was exactly what I just
said and I I I read this report and I
was really impressed
um so from what I can tell here
um this this individual found out that
the system that LinkedIn is using
um has this this concept of a of a urn
and uh I'll see if I can find the quote
right here
it is possible to trigger a urine
resolution by assigning a URL value to a
text field inside of the profile and
using a decoration expansion in a
voyager query so essentially what he
found out was that he could take this
this urn and I think in the report he
puts it in the um in the website field
um and this urn just for those of you
that are listening in the audio medium
looks like urn colon Li colon uh the the
object that you're looking at uh FS
underscore email address colon and then
the actual ID
um and so it's sort of like a structured
ID right and so he takes that he puts it
in the website field and when the call
he makes this call to the API to the
Voyager API on LinkedIn
um
that API will look at that urn that was
there and say okay um if this field is
urn then I need to resolve that urn so
it will go to the database pull that
value out and stick it in the included
field and I think he said that there was
some sort of
um
uh a parameter that allowed him to tell
it to resolve the included urns and then
that gets included in this little I said
included a lot of times in this little
included section in the response this
was the type of vulnerability that I've
I've not seen before and I have seen
these urns around so this is definitely
something to be aware of yeah super
interesting I think this urn stuff is
like maybe a Microsoft thing I don't I
don't know why it took me until today to
realize that Microsoft owns LinkedIn
yeah which is yeah it didn't which is
really interesting I I I I was just
looking at the Wikipedia apparently this
happened in 2016 but I never I don't
ever remember like maybe I just wasn't
paying attention at the time but just
missed yeah so I was like why are these
docs on the Microsoft on the
microsoft.com site and uh yeah that's
why that's really really interesting I
wonder uh where else you could use this
within Microsoft own services
yeah I totally I totally agree and I I
want to say there was even some mention
of this in the um in the write-up that
Sam Curry did on the Starbucks uh bug
that we found together leaking the 99
million records on Starbucks so
um that could definitely be something to
to keep your eye on it like we always
say you know these sort of things are
the kind of things we'd love to cover
the most here new techniques coming out
um stuff you all ought to be aware of so
we'll link this uh report in the in the
description uh definitely go check it
out and shout out to ultra power the uh
the guy who found this film
um this is really really good one super
awesome
cool you got anything else all right man
that's it for me alrighty catch you next
week then
sweet that's the pause
yo thanks for watching this episode of
critical thinking by Johnny podcast hope
you enjoyed it
um if you wouldn't mind head over to
YouTube and subscribe to our YouTube
channel at youtube.com critical thinking
podcast also drop a follow And subscribe
on your podcast app of choice uh we will
be soon launching a website at
criticalthinkingpodcast.io please head
over there as well there will be a
newsletter sign up where you can get
notifications for each episodes as well
as check out some transcription slash
blog summaries of the episodes which uh
which might be of interest to you thanks
see you next week
[Music]
thank you